Guide to the Actors' Equity Association Records WAG.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Contracts/Agreements/Codes
  - Subseries C: Off-Broadway
    - Electra:"closed", Dec 8, 1974 (Box 197, Folder 13)
    - Electra and Harlequinade:"closed", Feb 28, 1959 (Box 197, Folder 14)
    - Electra and Twelfth Night, 1962 (Box 197, Folder 15)
    - Electronic Nigger and Others:"closed", May 26, 1968 (Box 197, Folder 16)
    - Emperor:"closed", May 5, 1963 (Box 197, Folder 17)
    - Empire Builders:"closed", Oct 9, 1968 (Box 197, Folder 18)
    - Enclave:"closed", Dec 2, 1973 (Box 197, Folder 19)
    - End as a Man:"closed", Oct 21, 1953 (Box 197, Folder 20)
    - End of All Things Natural:"closed", Sep 14, 1959 (Box 197, Folder 21)
    - Endecott and the Red Cross:"closed", May 18, 1968 (Box 197, Folder 22)
    - Entertain a Ghost:"closed", Apr 15, 1962 (Box 197, Folder 23)
    - Epitaph for George Dillon:"closed", Mar 12, 1961 (Box 197, Folder 24)
    - Ergo:"closed", Apr 14, 1968 (Box 197, Folder 25)
    - Esther:"closed", Dec 4, 1977 (Box 197, Folder 26)
    - Evening with Max Morath:"closed", Jan 14, 1970 (Box 197, Folder 27)
    - Every Other Evil, 1961 (Box 197, Folder 28)
    - Evil that Men Do:"closed", Nov 1, 1970 (Box 197, Folder 29)
    - Exception and the Rule and The Prodigal Son:"closed", Sep 19, 1965 (Box 197, Folder 30)
    - Exhibition: "closed", May 28, 1969 (Box 197, Folder 31)
    - Experiment: "closed", May 21, 1967 (Box 197, Folder 32)
    - F. Jasmine Adams:"closed", Oct 31, 1971 (Box 197, Folder 33)
    - F.O.B.:"closed", Nov 26, 1972 (Box 197, Folder 34)
    - Faggot:"closed", Nov 25, 1973 (Box 197, Folder 35)
    - Failures, 1959 (Box 197, Folder 36)
    - Fallout, 1959 (Box 197, Folder 37)
    - Family Portrait:"closed", May 24, 1959 (Box 197, Folder 38)
    - Fantasticks: files for 1968 and 1974; show "closed", Jan 13, 2002 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Fashion:"closed", Mar 3, 1959 (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Fashion:"closed", Apr 16, 1974 (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Father Uxbridge Wants to Marry:"closed", Nov 11, 1967 (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Father:"closed", Dec 2, 1973 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - Feast of Panthers:"closed", Mar 22, 1961 (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - Feedlot:"closed", Nov 19, 1977 (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - Felix:"closed", Jan 20, 1974 (Box 198, Folder 8)
    - Fig Leaf in Her Bonnet:"closed", Jul 2, 1961 (Box 198, Folder 9)
    - Finn MacKool, the Grand Distraction:"closed", Sep 29, 1975 (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - Firebugs:"closed", Feb 17, 1963 (Box 198, Folder 11)
    - Firebugs:"closed", Jul 7, 1968 (Box 198, Folder 12)
    - Fireworks: "closed", Jun 14, 1969 (Box 198, Folder 13)
    - Fishing:"closed", Mar 9, 1975 (Box 198, Folder 14)
    - Five Evenings:"closed", May 12, 1963 (Box 198, Folder 15)
    - Five on the Black Hand Side:"closed", Jan 31, 1970 (Box 198, Folder 16)
    - Fixed:"closed", Dec 22, 1978 (Box 198, Folder 17)
    - For Colored Girls Who Have Considered Suicide When the Rainbow Was Enough:"closed", Aug 29, 1976 (Box 198, Folder 18)
    - Fortune and Men's Eyes:"closed", Jan 21, 1968 (Box 198, Folder 19)
    - Fortune and Men's Eyes:"closed", May 10, 1970 (Box 198, Folder 20)
    - Four Friends:"closed", Mar 17, 1968 (Box 198, Folder 21)
    - Four Friends:"closed", Feb 17, 1975 (Box 198, Folder 22)
    - Foursome:"closed", Dec 2, 1973 (Box 198, Folder 23)
    - Fourth Pig: "closed", Jan 27, 1965 (Box 198, Folder 24)
    - Fourth Wall: "closed", Jan 5, 1969 (Box 198, Folder 25)
    - Fragments: "closed", Oct 22, 1967 (Box 198, Folder 26)
    - Friday Night:"closed", Feb 28, 1965 (Box 198, Folder 27)
    - From the Second City:"closed", Nov 9, 1969 (Box 198, Folder 28)
    - Funny House of a Negro:"closed", Feb 9, 1964 (Box 198, Folder 29)
    - Futz:"closed", Dec 31, 1968 (Box 198, Folder 30)
    - Galgenhumor, 1961 (Box 198, Folder 31)
    - Gallows Humor:"closed", May 21, 1961 (Box 198, Folder 32)
    - Garden District:"closed", Jul 13, 1958 (Box 198, Folder 33)
    - Gaughin in Tahiti:"closed", Jan 2, 1977 (Box 198, Folder 34)
    - Geranium Hat:"closed", Apr 12, 1959 (Box 198, Folder 35)
    - Get Thee to Canterbury:"closed", Feb 9, 1969 (Box 198, Folder 36)
    - Ghosts:"closed", Apr 1, 1962 (Box 198, Folder 37)
    - Ghosts:"closed", May 27, 1973 (Box 198, Folder 38)
    - Giants' Dance:"closed", Nov 21, 1964 (Box 198, Folder 39)
    - Gift of the Magi:"closed", Jan 15, 1976 (Box 198, Folder 40)
    - Ginger Man: "closed", Jan 5, 1964 (Box 198, Folder 41)
    - Glorious Age:"closed", May 18, 1975 (Box 198, Folder 42)
    - Glorious Ruler:"closed", Jul 6, 1979 (Box 198, Folder 43)
    - Go Fly a Kite:"closed", Oct 16, 1969 (Box 198, Folder 44)
    - Go Show Me a Dragon:"closed", Oct 29, 1961 (Box 198, Folder 45)
    - GOA:"closed", Mar 17, 1968 (Box 198, Folder 46)
    - God Bless Coney:"closed", May 5, 1972 (Box 198, Folder 47)
    - God Bless You, Harold Fineberg:"closed", Apr 5, 1969 (Box 198, Folder 48)
    - God, Man and You, Baby:"closed", Oct 29, 1963 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - God Says There Is No Peter Ott:"closed", Apr 23, 1972 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Godspell:[correspondence Sep 1971-Dec 1972 and programs] "closed", Jun 13, 1976 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Godspell:[correspondence Jan 1973-Aug 1976] "closed", Jun 13, 1976 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Gogo Loves You:"closed", Oct 10, 1964 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Gogol:"closed", Dec 19, 1976 (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - Golden Apple:"closed", May 20, 1962 (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - Golden Screw:"closed", Mar 5, 1967 (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - Golden Six: "closed", Nov 8, 1959 (Box 199, Folder 9)
    - Golem, 1959 (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - Good Day and The Exhaustion of Our Son's Love:"closed", Dec 12, 1965 (Box 199, Folder 11)
    - Good Soldier Schweik:"closed", Apr 14, 1963 (Box 199, Folder 12)
    - Goose:"closed", Apr 10, 1960 (Box 199, Folder 13)
    - Gorilla Queen:"closed", Jun 17, 1967 (Box 199, Folder 14)
    - Grab Bag:"closed", Dec 1, 1968 (Box 199, Folder 15)
    - Great Scot: "closed", Dec 12, 1965 (Box 199, Folder 16)
    - Great Western Union:"closed", Feb 13, 1965 (Box 199, Folder 17)
    - Green Julia: "closed", Mar 25, 1973 (Box 199, Folder 18)
    - Green Pond: "closed", Dec 18, 1977 (Box 199, Folder 19)
    - Guests of the Nation, 1958 (Box 199, Folder 20)
    - Guitar:"closed", Nov 11, 1959 (Box 199, Folder 21)
    - Gun Play:"closed", Nov 14, 1971 (Box 199, Folder 22)
    - Hair:"closed", Dec 10, 1967 (Box 199, Folder 23)
    - Hairy Ape: "closed", Mar 21, 1976 (Box 199, Folder 24)
    - Half Past Wednesday:"closed", Apr 29, 1962 (Box 199, Folder 25)
    - Hamlet:"closed", Feb 11, 1968 (Box 199, Folder 26)
    - Hamp:"closed", Jun 4, 1967 (Box 199, Folder 27)
    - Happiness Cage:"closed", Nov 1, 1970 (Box 199, Folder 28)
    - Happy Birthday, Wanda June:"closed", Mar 14, 1971 (Box 199, Folder 29)
    - Happy Days: "closed", Nov 3, 1961 (Box 199, Folder 30)
    - Happy Days: "closed", Oct 10, 1965 (Box 199, Folder 31)
    - Happy End: "closed", Apr 30, 1977 (Box 199, Folder 32)
    - Happy Ending and Day of Absence:"closed", Jan 29, 1967 (Box 199, Folder 33)
    - Happy Hunting:"closed", Dec 18, 1977 (Box 199, Folder 34)
    - Happy Hypocrite:"closed", Sep 19, 1968 (Box 199, Folder 35)
    - Hark:"closed", Oct 1, 1972 (Box 199, Folder 36)
    - Harry, Noon and Night:"closed", May 9, 1965 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Hasty Heart: "closed", Aug 30, 1959 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Haunted Host:"closed", Nov 2, 1969 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Have I Got One for You:"closed", Jan 7, 1968 (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Hawk:"closed", Apr 28, 1968 (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Heaven and Earth:"closed", Apr 3, 1977 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Hedda Gabler:"closed", Apr 5, 1970 (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Helen:"closed", Dec 27, 1964 (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - Hello and Goodbye:"closed", Oct 26, 1969 (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Here Come the Clowns:"closed", Nov 19, 1960 (Box 200, Folder 10)
    - Hey You, Light Man:"closed", Apr 14, 1963 (Box 200, Folder 11)
    - Hi, Paisano: "closed", Oct 1, 1961 (Box 200, Folder 12)
    - Hobo:"closed", May 7, 1961 (Box 200, Folder 13)
    - Hogan's Goat:"closed", Apr 23, 1967 (Box 200, Folder 14)
    - Home Away from Home:"closed", May 4, 1969 (Box 200, Folder 15)
    - Home Movies: "closed", Jul 12, 1964 (Box 200, Folder 16)
    - Honest-to-God Schnozzola:"closed", Apr 27, 1969 (Box 200, Folder 17)
    - Honeymoon: "closed", May 23, 1975 (Box 200, Folder 18)
    - Hooray! It's a Glorious Day…and all that:"closed", Mar 20, 1966 (Box 200, Folder 19)
    - Hooters:"closed", Jun 4, 1978 (Box 200, Folder 20)
    - Hop, Signor: "closed", May 13, 1962 (Box 200, Folder 21)
    - Horseman, Pass By:"closed", Feb 16, 1969 (Box 200, Folder 22)
    - Hot L Baltimore:"closed", Jan 4, 1976 (Box 200, Folder 23)
    - Hothouse:"closed", Nov 10, 1974 (Box 200, Folder 24)
    - Hotel for Criminals:"closed", Jan 12, 1975 (Box 200, Folder 25)
    - Hotel Passionato:"closed", Oct 31, 1965 (Box 200, Folder 26)
    - House of Blue Leaves:"closed", Dec 4, 1971 (Box 200, Folder 27)
    - House of Flowers:"closed", Mar 17, 1968 (Box 200, Folder 28)
    - The House of Leather:"closed", Mar 18, 1970 (Box 200, Folder 29)
    - How Much, How Much?:"closed", May 10, 1970 (Box 200, Folder 30)
    - How to Get Rid of It:"closed", Nov 25, 1974 (Box 200, Folder 31)
    - How to Steal an Election:"closed", Dec 22, 1968 (Box 200, Folder 32)
    - Hunter:"closed", Jul 16, 1972 (Box 200, Folder 33)
    - Hustlers:"closed", Apr 20, 1975 (Box 200, Folder 34)
    - Huui, Huui: "closed", Dec 29, 1968 (Box 200, Folder 35)
    - I am a Woman:"closed", Apr 28, 1971 (Box 200, Folder 36)
    - I Dreamt I Dwelt in Bloomingdale's:"closed", Feb 15, 1970 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - I Got Shoes: "closed", Feb 10, 1963 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - I Love Thee Freely:"closed", Oct 7, 1973 (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - I Paid My Dues:"closed", May 23, 1976 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - I Want You: "closed", Sep 16, 1961 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Ice Age:"closed", Dec 14, 1975 (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Idiot:"closed", Oct 23, 1960 (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - Ignorants Abroad, 1960 (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - Immaculate Misconception:"closed", Oct 29, 1970 (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - Importance of Being Earnest:"closed", Jul 13, 1963 (Box 201, Folder 10)
    - Impudent Wolf:"closed", Nov 28, 1965 (Box 201, Folder 11)
    - In Case of Accident:"closed", Apr 2, 1972 (Box 201, Folder 12)
    - In Circles: "closed", May 12, 1968 (Box 201, Folder 13)
    - In New England Winter:"closed", Feb 7, 1971 (Box 201, Folder 14)
    - In the Boom Boom Room:"closed", Dec 15, 1974 (Box 201, Folder 15)
    - In the Summer House:"closed", Apr 5, 1964 (Box 201, Folder 16)
    - In the Time of Harry Harass:"closed", Oct 25, 1971 (Box 201, Folder 17)
    - In the Wine Time:"closed", May 15, 1976 (Box 201, Folder 18)
    - In White America:"closed", Jun 13, 1965 (Box 201, Folder 19)
    - Indian Wants the Bronx:"closed", Jul 14, 1968 (Box 201, Folder 20)
    - Infantry:"closed", Nov 20, 1966 (Box 201, Folder 21)
    - Innocent Ones, 1959 (Box 201, Folder 22)
    - Intimate Relations:"closed", Jan 5, 1963 (Box 201, Folder 23)
    - Invitation to a Beheading:"closed", May 4, 1969 (Box 201, Folder 24)
    - Ionescapade: "closed", May 5, 1974 (Box 201, Folder 25)
    - Iphigenia: "closed", Mar 8, 1972 (Box 201, Folder 26)
    - Iphigenia in Aulis:"closed", May 26, 1968 (Box 201, Folder 27)
    - Iphigenia in Tauris:"closed", Oct 11, 1959 (Box 201, Folder 28)
    - Istanbul:"closed", Feb 14, 1971 (Box 201, Folder 29)
    - Jack-in-the-Box, 1960 (Box 201, Folder 30)
    - Jackass:"closed", Mar 24, 1960 (Box 201, Folder 31)
    - Jackhammer: "closed", Feb 6, 1962 (Box 201, Folder 32)
    - Jackknife, 1958 (Box 201, Folder 33)
    - Jacques Brel is Alive and Well and Living in Paris: Astor Place Theatre "closed", Sep 1, 1974 (Box 201, Folder 34)
    - Jamimma:"closed", Jul 6, 1972 (Box 201, Folder 35)
    - Javelin:"closed", Nov 20, 1966 (Box 201, Folder 36)
    - Jesse and the Bandit Queen:"closed", Feb 29, 1976 (Box 201, Folder 37)
    - Jo:"closed", Apr 5, 1964 (Box 201, Folder 38)
    - Joan:"closed", Aug 13, 1972 (Box 201, Folder 39)
    - Jockeys:"closed", Apr 17, 1977 (Box 201, Folder 40)
    - John Brown's Body: "closed", [Aug 21, 1960] (Box 201, Folder 41)
    - Jonah:"closed", Feb 27, 1966 (Box 201, Folder 42)
    - Journey of the Fifth Horse:"closed", Apr 30, 1966 (Box 201, Folder 43)
    - Journey to the Day:"closed", Dec 1, 1963 (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Journey with Strangers:"closed", [Dec 7, 1958] (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - Jumping Fool:"closed", Feb 22, 1970 (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Justice Box: "closed", Jun 6, 1971 (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - Kaddish:"closed", May 14, 1972 (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - Kaspar:"closed", Mar 18, 1973 (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - Kid Champion:"closed", Mar 9, 1975 (Box 202, Folder 7)
    - Killdeer:"closed", Apr 21, 1974 (Box 202, Folder 8)
    - Killer:"closed", Apr 3, 1960 (Box 202, Folder 9)
    - Kingdom of Earth:"closed", Jun 25, 1976 (Box 202, Folder 10)
    - Kiss Mama: "closed", Jan 24, 1965 (Box 202, Folder 11)
    - Kitchen:"closed", Oct 9, 1966 (Box 202, Folder 12)
    - Kittiwake Island:"closed", Oct 16, 1960 (Box 202, Folder 13)
    - Knack:"closed", Jan 9, 1966 (Box 202, Folder 14)
    - Krapp's Last Tape and Zoo Story:"closed", Nov 20, 1960 (Box 202, Folder 15)
    - Kumquat in the Persimmon Tree:"closed", Jun 30, 1962 (Box 202, Folder 16)
    - La Ronde:"closed", [Jan 1, 1961] (Box 202, Folder 17)
    - La Turista: "closed", Apr 1, 1967 (Box 202, Folder 18)
    - Lady Audley's Secret:"closed", Oct 8, 1972 (Box 202, Folder 19)
    - Lady of the Manor, 1958 (Box 202, Folder 20)
    - Landscape of the Body:"closed", Nov 20, 1977 (Box 202, Folder 21)
    - Last Analysis:"closed", Aug 1, 1971 (Box 202, Folder 22)
    - Last Chord: closed May 23, 1976, re-opened Jul 22, 1976, "closed", Aug 15, 1976 (Box 202, Folder 23)
    - Last Days of the British Honduras:"closed", Nov 24, 1974 (Box 202, Folder 24)
    - Last Known Position at the Battle of Poitiers and The Strindberg Brothers:"closed", Jun 30, 1968 (Box 202, Folder 25)
    - Last Minstrel and Save Me a Place at Forest Lawn:"closed", [Jun 9, 1963] (Box 202, Folder 26)
    - Last Sweet Days of Isaac:"closed", May 2, 1971 (Box 202, Folder 27)
    - Laughwind: "closed", Mar 6, 1966 (Box 202, Folder 28)
    - Laundry:"closed", Mar 10, 1963 (Box 202, Folder 29)
    - Leave It to Jane:"closed", Aug 13, 1961 (Box 202, Folder 30)
    - Leaves of Grass:"closed", Oct 24, 1971 (Box 202, Folder 31)
    - Legend of Lovers:"closed", Nov 22, 1959 (Box 202, Folder 32)
    - Legitimate Steal, 1958 (Box 202, Folder 33)
    - Leonard Bernstein's Theatre Songs:"closed", Sep 12, 1965 (Box 202, Folder 34)
    - Les Femmes Noires:"closed", Apr 14, 1974 (Box 202, Folder 35)
    - L'Ete: "closed", Apr 18, 1973 (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - Life is a Dream:"closed", May 11, 1964 (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - Lime Green Khaki Blue:"closed", Apr 5, 1969 (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - Lincoln Live:"closed", Dec 26, 1976 (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - Lion in Love:"closed", Apr 28, 1963 (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Little Boxes:"closed", Dec 14, 1969 (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - Little Eyolf:"closed", Apr 14, 1964 (Box 203, Folder 7)
    - Little Mary Sunshine:"closed", Sep 2, 1962 (Box 203, Folder 8)
    - Little Murders:"closed", Nov 30, 1969 (Box 203, Folder 9)
    - Live Like Pigs:"closed", Sep 26, 1965 (Box 203, Folder 10)
    - Living Theatre: Julian Beck and Judith Malina, 1958-1960 (Box 203, Folder 11)
    - Living Theatre: Julian Beck and Judith Malina, 1961-1962 (Box 203, Folder 12)
    - Local Stigmatic:"closed", Nov 9, 1969 (Box 203, Folder 13)
    - Long and the Short and the Tall:"closed", Apr 15, 1962 (Box 203, Folder 14)
    - Long Gallery, 1958 (Box 203, Folder 15)
    - Long Grass: "abandoned", Nov 8, 1965 (Box 203, Folder 16)
    - Long Time Coming and a Long Time Gone:"closed", Nov 21, 1971 (Box 203, Folder 17)
    - Look Back in Anger:"closed", Feb 15, 1959 (Box 203, Folder 18)
    - Look Where I'm At:"closed", Mar 8, 1971 (Box 203, Folder 19)
    - Lotta or The Best Thing Evolution's Ever Come Up With:"closed", Dec 2, 1973 (Box 203, Folder 20)
    - Louis and the Elephant:"closed", Nov 6, 1971 (Box 203, Folder 21)
    - Love and Let Love:"closed", Jan 14, 1968 (Box 203, Folder 22)
    - Love and Maple Syrup:"closed", Jan 18, 1970 (Box 203, Folder 23)
    - Love, Love, Love:"closed", Jul 3, 1977 (Box 203, Folder 24)
    - Love Me, Love My Children:"closed" [re-opened, see next folder 25 ], Dec 12, 1971 (Box 203, Folder 25)
    - Love Me, Love My Children:[same production, new producer] "closed", Apr 23, 1972 (Box 203, Folder 26)
    - Love Nest: "closed", Feb 3, 1963 (Box 203, Folder 27)
    - Love of Two Hours:"closed", Oct 28, 1962 (Box 203, Folder 28)
    - Love Your Crooked Neighbor:"closed", Jan 4, 1970 (Box 203, Folder 29)
    - Lovers:"closed", May 11, 1975 (Box 203, Folder 30)
    - Lovers in the Metro:"closed", Feb 10, 1962 (Box 203, Folder 31)
    - Ludlow Fair and The Madness of Lady Bright:"closed", Apr 3, 1966 (Box 203, Folder 32)
    - Lulu:"closed", Oct 12, 1958 (Box 203, Folder 33)
    - Lulu, 1976 (Box 203, Folder 34)
    - Lyle:"closed", Mar 21, 1970 (Box 203, Folder 35)
    - Lysistrata: "closed", May 24, 1959 (Box 203, Folder 36)
    - Machinal:"closed", Jun 12, 1960 (Box 203, Folder 37)
    - Mad Show:"closed", Sep 10, 1967 (Box 203, Folder 38)
    - Madame Aphrodite:"closed", Jan 7, 1962 (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Magic of Jolson:"closed", Apr 13, 1975 (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Magic Weave: "closed", Dec 31, 1961 (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - Magistrate: Off-Broadway non-Equity show with Equity Members, 1959 (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Magnificent Hugo:"closed", Apr 7, 1961 (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Maids, 1956 (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - Maids:"closed", Jan 5, 1964 (Box 204, Folder 7)
    - Make Me Disappear:"closed", May 18, 1969 (Box 204, Folder 8)
    - Mailing of Moo, 1958 (Box 204, Folder 9)
    - Man and Superman, 1960 (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - Man of Destiny, 1962 (Box 204, Folder 11)
    - Man Out Loud, Girl Quiet:"closed", Apr 15, 1962 (Box 204, Folder 12)
    - Man Who Got Away, 1977 (Box 204, Folder 13)
    - Man With a Load of Mischief:"closed", Jun 4, 1967 (Box 204, Folder 14)
    - Man With the Flower in His Mouth:"closed", Jun 29, 1969 (Box 204, Folder 15)
    - Mandragola: "closed", Jun 1, 1958 (Box 204, Folder 16)
    - Marching Song, 1959 (Box 204, Folder 17)
    - Marco Polo Sings a Solo:"closed", Mar 6, 1977 (Box 204, Folder 18)
    - Marcus in the High Grass:"closed", Dec 4, 1960 (Box 204, Folder 19)
    - Masquerade: "closed", Nov 28, 1971 (Box 204, Folder 20)
    - Master Builder:"closed", Dec 19, 1971 (Box 204, Folder 21)
    - Matter of Life and Death:"closed", Nov 10, 1963 (Box 204, Folder 22)
    - Matter of Time:"closed", Apr 27, 1975 (Box 204, Folder 23)
    - Matty and the Moron and Madonna:"closed", Apr 25, 1965 (Box 204, Folder 24)
    - Me Nobody Knows:"closed", Nov 1, 1970 (Box 204, Folder 25)
    - Medal of Honor Rag:"closed", May 2, 1976 (Box 204, Folder 26)
    - Medea:"closed", Dec 2, 1973 (Box 204, Folder 27)
    - Meet Peter Grant:"closed", Jun 3, 1961 (Box 204, Folder 28)
    - Memory Bank: "closed", Feb 1, 1970 (Box 204, Folder 29)
    - Memphis is Gone:"closed", Feb 13, 1977 (Box 204, Folder 30)
    - Memphis Store-Bought Teeth:"closed", Jan 2, 1972 (Box 204, Folder 31)
    - Merchant of Venice:"closed", Mar 4, 1962 (Box 204, Folder 32)
    - Mercy Me:"abandoned", 1968 (Box 204, Folder 33)
    - Mercy Street:"closed", Nov 21, 1969 (Box 204, Folder 34)
    - Midnight Caller:"closed", [Jul 13, 1958] (Box 204, Folder 35)
    - Midsummer Night's Dream:"closed", Aug 29, 1964 (Box 204, Folder 36)
    - Midsummer Night's Dream:"closed", Jul 23, 1967 (Box 204, Folder 37)
    - Mikado:"closed", Nov 14, 1971 (Box 204, Folder 38)
    - Mikado:"closed", Nov 17, 1974 (Box 204, Folder 39)
    - Millionairess:"closed", Mar 16, 1969 (Box 204, Folder 40)
    - Misalliance: "closed", Apr 30, 1972 (Box 204, Folder 41)
    - Misanthrope: "closed", Nov 27, 1977 (Box 204, Folder 42)
    - Miss Emily Adams:"closed", Apr 16, 1960 (Box 204, Folder 43)
    - Miss Julie and The Death of Lord Chatterly:"closed", Aug 12, 1973 (Box 204, Folder 44)
    - Miss Margarida's Way:"closed", Sep 4, 1977 (Box 204, Folder 45)
    - Miss Pete and The Floor (Doubles and Opposites):"closed", May 25, 1966 (Box 204, Folder 46)
    - Mr. Simian: "closed", Nov 9, 1963 (Box 204, Folder 47)
    - Mistresses and Maidens:"closed", Feb 8, 1959 (Box 204, Folder 48)
    - Mod Donna: "closed", Jun 7, 1970 (Box 204, Folder 49)
    - Monopoly:"closed", Apr 17, 1966 (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Monsters:"closed", May 1, 1977 (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - Month in the Country:"closed", Jul 7, 1963 (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Month of Sundays:"closed", Sep 22, 1968 (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Montserrat, 1961 (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Moon Dreamers:"closed", Dec 28, 1969 (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - Moon for the Misbegotten:"closed", Dec 1, 1968 (Box 205, Folder 7)
    - Moon in the Yellow River:"closed", [Mar 26, 1961] (Box 205, Folder 8)
    - Moonchildren:"closed", Oct 20, 1974 (Box 205, Folder 9)
    - More Than You Deserve:"closed", Jan 13, 1974 (Box 205, Folder 10)
    - Morning Sun: "closed", Oct 13, 1963 (Box 205, Folder 11)
    - Moths:"closed", May 11, 1970 (Box 205, Folder 12)
    - Mousetrap: "closed", Apr 23, 1961 (Box 205, Folder 13)
    - Mrs. Warren's Profession:"closed", May 5, 1963 (Box 205, Folder 14)
    - Mummers and Men:"closed", Mar 31, 1962 (Box 205, Folder 15)
    - Murder of Me:"closed", May 27, 1962 (Box 205, Folder 16)
    - Music Magic: "closed", Jan 9, 1977 (Box 205, Folder 17)
    - Muzeeka and Red Cross:"closed", Jun 23, 1968 (Box 205, Folder 18)
    - My House is Your House:"closed", Oct 16, 1971 (Box 205, Folder 19)
    - My Life:"closed", Feb 27, 1977 (Box 205, Folder 20)
    - My Wife and I:"closed", Oct 22, 1966 (Box 205, Folder 21)
    - Mystery Play:"closed", Jan 14, 1973 (Box 205, Folder 22)
    - Naomi Court: "closed", Nov 17, 1974 (Box 205, Folder 23)
    - Nat Turner: "closed", Nov 6, 1960 (Box 205, Folder 24)
    - Nathan the Wise:"closed", Apr 1, 1962 (Box 205, Folder 25)
    - Nature of the Crime:"closed", Apr 12, 1970 (Box 205, Folder 26)
    - Nellie Toole & Co.:"closed", Oct 21, 1973 (Box 205, Folder 27)
    - Nest:"closed", Apr 9, 1970 (Box 205, Folder 28)
    - New Man:"closed", Sep 26, 1976 (Box 205, Folder 29)
    - New York City Street Show:"closed", May 15, 1977 (Box 205, Folder 30)
    - New York Shakespeare Festival: All shows (blanket bond), 1973-1976 (Box 205, Folder 31)
    - Niggerlovers:"closed", Oct 22, 1967 (Box 205, Folder 32)
    - Night is Black Bottles:"closed", Dec 8, 1962 (Box 205, Folder 33)
    - Night of the Dunce:"closed", Feb 5, 1967 (Box 205, Folder 34)
    - Night Shift: "closed", Nov 6, 1977 (Box 205, Folder 35)
    - Nightclub Cantata:"closed", May 15, 1977 (Box 205, Folder 36)
    - No Exit, 1954 (Box 205, Folder 37)
    - No Exit, 1955 (Box 205, Folder 38)
    - No Exit and The Little Private World of Arthur Morton Fenwick:"closed", Nov 5, 1967 (Box 205, Folder 39)
    - No Place to Be Somebody:"closed", Dec 13, 1969 (Box 205, Folder 40)
    - No Trifling With Love, 1959 (Box 205, Folder 41)
    - Nobody Hears a Broken Drum:"closed", Mar 22, 1970 (Box 205, Folder 42)
    - Not a Way of Life:"closed", Mar 26, 1967 (Box 205, Folder 43)
    - Not While I'm Eating:"closed", [Dec 21, 1961] (Box 205, Folder 44)
    - Nourish the Beast:"closed", Nov 18, 1973 (Box 205, Folder 45)
    - Now:"closed", Jun 23, 1968 (Box 205, Folder 46)
    - Now Is the Time for All Good Men:"closed", Dec 31, 1967 (Box 205, Folder 47)
    - Nuns:"closed", Jun 1, 1970 (Box 205, Folder 48)
    - O Say Can You See:"closed", Nov 2, 1962 (Box 205, Folder 49)